adtech.info 2014-10-24

# ADTECH Ad Server Solutions - Updated Privacy Policy

Effective September 15, 2014 the ADTECH Privacy Policy will be updated. To learn more about these updates, please review the [updated Privacy Policy](http://privacy.aol.com/updated_policy) or visit our [Frequently Asked Questions](http://privacy.aol.com/faq/).

We appreciate your visit to the website of ADTECH GmbH (hereafter referred to as "ADTECH"). Thank you for your interest in our company, our products, and our webpages.  
As we put great emphasis on the protection of your privacy when you use our webpages, we utilize your data in accordance with the statutory data protection regulations. Below, we inform you about how we handle your data.  
On this website, ADTECH collects various data and information about you: 

## Web server logs

You can always visit our webpages without disclosing your identity. However, like most other websites, the server on which our webpages are hosted (hereafter referred to as "Web server") automatically collects information from you when you visit us on the Internet.  
The Web server automatically identifies certain personal data such as your IP address, the date and the time of your visit to our page, the pages on our website that you visit, the website that you are coming from, your browser (e.g. Mozilla Firefox), your operating system (e.g. Windows 7), and the domain name and address of your Internet service provider (e.g. AOL). For webpages that use cookies (as explained below), the Web server also logs this information.  
We regularly analyze these server logs in anonymous form for statistical purposes (click stream analyses) in order to find out how our webpages are used. Based on this insight, we optimize our website.  
Additionally, we may use this information in collaboration with your Internet service provider and/or local authorities in the event of system abuse in order to identify the origin of the abuse. 

## Cookies

Some of our webpages use cookie technology. A cookie is a piece of information that our Web server sends to your computer (more precisely, that is stored in your browser directory) as soon as you visit the website.  
You can prevent the setting of cookies by configuring your browser software accordingly. If necessary, consult the manufacturer's website for instructions on how to do this. If you decide not to allow cookies to be stored on your computer, you will still have access to most of our webpages. However, you may not be able to fully use certain functions of our webpages.  
We only permit third parties to place cookies on your computer via these webpages within the scope of Web analysis. Details are described below under "Web analysis." 

## Web analysis

This website uses the Web analysis services described in detail below.  
This website uses Piwik, a Web analysis software system that enables the statistical analysis of visitor traffic. The analysis of your use of the website is based on cookies. General information on cookies and on how you can prevent the use of cookies is provided above under "Cookies." Additionally, Piwik anonymizes your IP address.  
Web analysis with Piwik takes place exclusively on the servers of ADTECH. 

## Social plugins

On some of our webpages, we have integrated social plugins ("plugins") of the following social networks: Facebook, Twitter, Google+, and LinkedIn. The plugins consist of buttons marked with the logo of the respective network.  
In connection with the integration of social plugins in our webpages, we pay careful attention to the protection of your privacy. Therefore, all plugins integrated into our webpages are initially disabled and need to be activated by you in case you wish to use them.  
By activating the social plugins, you agree to the loading of the content of the respective plugins directly from the servers of the respective network operator and to the integration into our website. As a result, your browser will establish a direct connection to the servers of the respective network operator and transmit the information specified above under "Web server logs" to the network operator's Web servers as well. Among other things, the network operator will learn that you have accessed the respective webpage of our website. If you have an account with the respective social network and are logged in, the network operator can link the aforementioned automatically transmitted information to the information stored in your account. This will happen even if you have not yet clicked on the activated button.  
Subsequently, whenever you interact with the plugin, i.e. click on the button or enter a comment, the information will be sent directly from the browser to the respective network, where it will be stored.  
For information on the further processing and use of the data by the respective network operator and your rights and configuration options in connection with the protection of your privacy, please refer to the data protection notice of the respective network operator. 

## Collection, processing, use, and transmission of personal data beyond the scope of Web server logs

Beyond the scope of the Web server logs, we only collect data from you if you actively disclose such data to us in order to use one of the services we offer (e.g. in inquiries via our website, when using the internal customer zone, or to sign up for our e-mail newsletter). This data will be processed and/or used exclusively for the performance of the respective service. 

## International data transfer

Your stored personal data is not processed outside countries of the European Union or of the European Economic Area (EU/EEA). 

## Security

Please note that the transmission of data on the Internet is not secure and that third parties might intercept and use the data. You can also contact us by mail or telephone. 

## Minors

Children and adolescents under the age of 14 are not permitted to transmit personal data on the Internet without parental or guardian permission. Please note that our webpages are not intended or designed for adolescents under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personal data of persons under the age of 18. 

## Links to other websites

This website also contains links to other websites. However, the privacy policy described here does not apply to such websites. Please visit the respective websites directly for information on the data protection, security, collection of data, and regulations concerning the forwarding of data. ADTECH does not accept any liability for measures originating from such websites or for their contents. 

## Information

If you have any further questions on the subject of "data protection at ADTECH," please contact the following address:

ADTECH GmbH  
Robert-Bosch-Str. 32  
63303 Dreieich  
Germany

Revision: 10/2012
